[{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980255277,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":21903,"timeElapsed":62004},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980267363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":12084,"timeElapsed":74090},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980275691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":8327,"timeElapsed":82418},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980282101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":6409,"timeElapsed":88828},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980292231,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":10129,"timeElapsed":98957},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980302097,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":9865,"timeElapsed":108824},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980311855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":9756,"timeElapsed":118582},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980316425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":4569,"timeElapsed":123152},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980321123,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4697,"timeElapsed":127850},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980341513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":18747,"timeElapsed":148240},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980348989,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":7475,"timeElapsed":155716},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980354726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":5736,"timeElapsed":161453},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980358352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3625,"timeElapsed":165079},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980365891,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":7537,"timeElapsed":172618},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980370237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4345,"timeElapsed":176964},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980378481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":8243,"timeElapsed":185207},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980386509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":8027,"timeElapsed":193236},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980390915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4405,"timeElapsed":197642},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980401815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":9536,"timeElapsed":208541},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980408251,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":6435,"timeElapsed":214978},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980415985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7732,"timeElapsed":222712},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980421347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5361,"timeElapsed":228074},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980427574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6226,"timeElapsed":234301},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980430591,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3015,"timeElapsed":237318},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980435969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":5376,"timeElapsed":242696},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980439901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3931,"timeElapsed":246628},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980445249,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5347,"timeElapsed":251976},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980461467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":14847,"timeElapsed":268194},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980464175,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2707,"timeElapsed":270902},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980478361,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":14184,"timeElapsed":285087},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980486061,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7699,"timeElapsed":292788},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980511617,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":25555,"timeElapsed":318344},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980515100,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3482,"timeElapsed":321827},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980519471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":4369,"timeElapsed":326198},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980523269,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3797,"timeElapsed":329996},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980528517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5247,"timeElapsed":335244},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980540621,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":10757,"timeElapsed":347348},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980545637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":5016,"timeElapsed":352364},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980556463,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":10825,"timeElapsed":363190},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980559274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2810,"timeElapsed":366001},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980564075,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4800,"timeElapsed":370802},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980566952,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2876,"timeElapsed":373679},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980571903,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4949,"timeElapsed":378630},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980575317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3412,"timeElapsed":382044},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980579347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4029,"timeElapsed":386074},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980592493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":11691,"timeElapsed":399220},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980599737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":7244,"timeElapsed":406464},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980608919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":9181,"timeElapsed":415646},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980612941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4021,"timeElapsed":419668},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980632693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":19751,"timeElapsed":439420},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980635205,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2510,"timeElapsed":441932},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980639386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4181,"timeElapsed":446113},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980641711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2324,"timeElapsed":448438},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980646408,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4697,"timeElapsed":453135},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980666649,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":18048,"timeElapsed":473376},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980669329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2679,"timeElapsed":476056},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980678889,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":9558,"timeElapsed":485616},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980681269,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2379,"timeElapsed":487996},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980684979,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":3709,"timeElapsed":491706},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980687204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":2224,"timeElapsed":493931},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980690941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3736,"timeElapsed":497668},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980696289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5347,"timeElapsed":503016},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980701719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":5429,"timeElapsed":508446},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980713775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":9544,"timeElapsed":520502},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980716227,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":2450,"timeElapsed":522954},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980720261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4033,"timeElapsed":526988},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980722557,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2294,"timeElapsed":529284},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980727155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4598,"timeElapsed":533882},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980731199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":4043,"timeElapsed":537926},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980734409,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3208,"timeElapsed":541135},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980737501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3091,"timeElapsed":544228},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980746742,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9241,"timeElapsed":553469},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980750281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3538,"timeElapsed":557008},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980761637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":9941,"timeElapsed":568364},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980765389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3750,"timeElapsed":572116},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980774206,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":8817,"timeElapsed":580933},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980776429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":2222,"timeElapsed":583156},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980781089,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4659,"timeElapsed":587816},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980786312,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":5222,"timeElapsed":593039},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980790487,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":4174,"timeElapsed":597214},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980793113,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2625,"timeElapsed":599840},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980796567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3453,"timeElapsed":603294},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980801997,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5429,"timeElapsed":608724},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980812853,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":9408,"timeElapsed":619580},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980814775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1920,"timeElapsed":621502},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980818693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3917,"timeElapsed":625420},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980820863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2169,"timeElapsed":627590},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980825297,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4433,"timeElapsed":632024},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980827351,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2053,"timeElapsed":634078},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980830685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3332,"timeElapsed":637412},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980833169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2484,"timeElapsed":639896},{"subjectID":"fckjlwqq42","prolificID":"5ea1e407df1e160c7db497c7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25758f7399c8aa25fba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980836613,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3442,"timeElapsed":643340}]